A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) FA489
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002)
1978-2004
1990-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA489
123.14 Cubic Feet 94 standard record storage boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Scope and Contents
Contains grant administration records.
- AC.2002.002: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2001; AC.2002.002; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.002.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 94001 #240 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INSTITUTE OF BOTANY - PHOTOPERIOD SENSITIVE MALE STERILITY IN CHINESE VARIETIES OF RICE, 1994-1998 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #249 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (CHINA) - GENETICS AND MOLECULAR BASES OF HETEROSIS IN HYBRID RICE, 1992-1998 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #251 - TRIBHUVAN UNIVERSITY - INSTITUTE OF AGRICULTURE AND ANIMAL SCIENCE (NEPAL) - GENETIC DIVERSITY OF XANTHOMONAS ORYZAE PV. ORYZAE, 1993-2000 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #254 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SHANGHAI INSTITUTE OF PLANT PHYSIOLOGY - ELICITORS AND HYPERSENSITIVE RESPONSE IN RICE, 1993-2000 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #262 - GUANGXI AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF RICE PLANT, 1993-1998 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #275 - INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY (VIETNAM) - ESTABLISH FACILITY FOR GENE MAPPING AND APPLICATION TO RICE IMPROVEMENT, 1994-1998 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #279 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR MAPPING OF GENES AND FERTILITY RESTORATION IN RICE, 1993-2000 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #280 - BEJING AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - SALT TOLERANCE MECHANISMS IN RICE, 1994-1998 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #286 - BOSE INSTITUTE - TRANSGENI C INDICA RICE PLANTS, 1989-2000 (Box R3440)
    - RF 94001 #290 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER FELLOWSHIP ON MAPPING GENES AND HETEROSIS IN RICE, 1994-1999 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94001 #292 - TEXAS A, 1994-2000 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94001 #301 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - GENES CONTROLLING CYTOPLASMIC MALE STERILITY IN RICE, 1994-1998 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94004 #1 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (DEPT. OF) - STRIGA CONTROL RESEARCH BY VERNON KABAMBE, 1992-2001 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94004 #4 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - MAIZE AND FERTILIZER IMPROVEMENT IN MALAWI, 1996-2001 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94004 #5 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - CREDIT AND AGRICULTURAL TECHNOLOGY, FOOD SECURITY AND NUTRITION IN MALAWI, 1996-1998 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94006 #28 - EARTH PLEDGE FOUNDATION - THE EARTH TIMES: 1994 U.N. CONFERENCE ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1996 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94006 #35 - JSI RESEARCH AND TRAINING INSTITUTE, INC. - EMPOWERMENT OF WOMEN AND FAMILY PLANNING IN BANGLADESH, 1991-1999 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94008 #61 - INTERNATIONAL ACADEMY OF THE ENVIRONMENT (SWITZERLAND) - LEAD PROGRAM IN INDIA, 1991-2000 (Box R3441)
    - RF 94010 #544 - DON GIOVANI A. C. - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS - PERFORMING ARTS, 1993-1998 (Box R3441)
    - RF 93038 #39; RF 94020 #40 - HAYES, IAN - ECONOMICS OF SOIL FERTILITY IN MAIZE PRODUCTION, 1994-2000 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94011 #16 - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - WEST AFRICAN MUSEUMS PROGRAMME - "MUSEUMS AND URBAN CULTURE" WORKSHOP, 1995-1997 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94012 #114 - LIBRARY FOUNDATION OF SAN FRANCISCO - CITY STORIES EXHIBITION, 1993-1997 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94012 #115 - GALERIA STUDIO 24 - (RE) GENERATION PROJECT, 1994-1997 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94012 #117 - DRAWING CENTER - EXHIBITION OF PLAINS INDIAN LEDGER DRAWINGS, 1994-1998 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94014 #126 - ON THE BOARDS - NEW WORKS COMMISSIONING PROGRAM, 1992-1996 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94020 #54 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - INTERCROPPING OF FORAGE LEGUMES WITH MAIZE AND FODDER GRASSES, 1994-2000 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94021 #3 - SHENYANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - MOLECULAR MARKER MAPPING OF GENES CONTROLLING APHID RESISTANCE IN SORGHUM LINES, 1993-1997 (Box R3442)
      - Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) (Item 2002.001.001)
    - RF 94021 #7 - TEXAS A, 1989-2001 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94022 #3 - RUKUNI, MANDIVAMBA - AFRICAN SMALLHOLDER AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2001 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94023 #53 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - MAIZE-LEGUME SYSTEMS IN THE STATE OF OAXACA, 1994-1998 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94024 #85 - PERL, SUSAN - POLICY EDUCATION AND COMMUNICATION RELATING TO HIV, 1995-1999 (Box R3442)
    - RF 94024 #93 - AUSTRALIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - HEALTH TRANSITION CENTRE - VULNERABILITY TO AIDS IN SOUTH ASIA, 1995-1999 (Box R3442)
    - RF 93031 #574; RF 94027 #575 - MUWANGA, NANSOZI - ADIA: DECENTRALIZING PRIMARY EDUCATION IN UGANDA, 1996-1997 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94025 #13 - POPULATION COUNCIL - INTERNATIONAL CONSORTIUM ON MALE CONTRACEPTION, 1993-1998 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94025 #25 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - EFFECT OF PEPTIDES ON SPERM, 1994-1998 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #579 - KAARIA, SUSAN - ADIA: ECONOMIC ROLE OF INDIGENOUS FRUITS IN MIOMBO WOODLANDS OF MALAWI, 1996-1999 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #583 - SENO, SIMON OLE - ADIA: STRATEGIES FOR ENHANCING LOCAL SUPPORT FOR CONSERVATION IN KENYA, 1995-1998 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #585 - BAOUA, IBRAHIM BOUKARY - ADIA: TROPHIC RELATIONSHIPS OF FORFICULA SENEGALENSIS SERVILLE ON BULRUSH MILLET, 1996-1997 (Box R3443)
    - RF 9027 #589 - OTISO, KEFA - ADIA: VOLUNTARY SECTOR IN URBAN PLANNING AND BASIC SERVICE IN NAIROBI, 1995-1999 (Box R3443)
    - RF 9027 #591 - GANA, BERTHA - ADIA: EFFECTS OF LAND USE CHANGES ON SOIL QUALITY IN GHANA, 1996-2000 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #593 - NYAMBARA, PIUS SHUNGUDZAPERA - ADIA: COTTON FARMERS IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1999 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #607 - MAGUTU, JERRY - ACA: "POPULARIZATION OF LOW COST HOUSE-BUILDING MATERIALS IN KENYA", 1996-1997 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #608 - MBAYE, ABDOU - ADIA: "PEPPER VEINAL MOTTLE POTYVIRUS IN CAPSICUM" IN SENEGAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #610 - MULWAFU, WAPULUMUKA - ADIA: "STATE, CONSERVATIONISM, AND SUSTAINABILITY IN A PEASANT ECONOMY IN MALAWI; 1860s-1964", 1996-2000 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94027 #612 - MANYARA, CHARLES GICHANA - ADIA: ASSESSING THE IMPACT OF THE TSETSE FLY ON LAND USE AND HUMAN WELFARE IN KENYA, 1996-1999 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94031 #41 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - "BIOLOGICAL MANAGEMENT OF SOIL FERTILITY IN MALAWI", 1993-1995 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94031 #42 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - ELECTRONIC MAIL ON THE CAMPUS, 1994-1999 (Box R3443)
    - RF 94031 #47 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - ELECTRONIC MAIL SERVICES, 1995-1999 (Box R3443)
- AC.2002.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1981-2001; AC.2002.003; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.003.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 93039 #91; RF 94033 #92 - NICHOLSON, CHARLES FREDERICK - SSRF: DOMESTIC DAIRY PRODUCTION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1992-2001 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94031 #48 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - ELECTRONIC MAIL SERVICES, 1995-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94031 #58 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - DRAUGHT ANIMAL AND CROP MANAGEMENT FOR IMPROVED CROP PRODUCTIVITY, 1993-1996 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94033 #94 - DONOVAN, CYNTHIA - SSRF: SERVE AS AGRICULTURAL ECONOMIST IN RICE PROGRAM, 1994-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94033 #97 - ELBASHA, ELAMIN HAMODA - SSRF: RESEARCH PRIORITY SETTING FOR ILRI, 1994-1998 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94034 #454 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH (BANGLADESH) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY STUDIES, 1994-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94035 #32 - PEKING UNION MEDICAL COLLEGE (CHINA) - UNION SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH - PUBLIC HEALTH IN CHINA, 1993-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #211 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - NEW WORKS FOR COLTRANE PROJECT OF PHILADELPHIA, 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #212 - BAY AREA WOMEN'S PHILHARMONIC - CHEN YI CONCERTS PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #213 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - "THE THIRTEENTH TRIBE", 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #212 - BAY AREA WOMEN'S PHILHARMONIC - CHEN YI CONCERTS PROJECT - MYTHS AND POEMS OF CHINA - Digital, 1996 June 15; 2002.003.001; Digital (Item 2002.003.001)
    - RF 94043 #214 - HOUSE FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - "MILLENIUM PROJECT", 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #215 - PHILADELPHIA DANCE COMPANY - DANCE WORKS BY PHILADELPHIA DANCE PROJECTS PROGRAM, 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #216 - MIAMI-DADE COMMUNITY COLLEGE - OPERA, "BALSEROS", 1995-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #217 - LIMON DANCE FOUNDATION - DANCE-THEATER WORK "HEART BEATS", 1995-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #218 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - "THE GATEWAYS PROGRAM", 1995-1999 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #220 - BOROUGH OF MANHATTAN COMMUNITY COLLEGE PERFORMING ARTS CENTER - THEATRICAL WORK "HOLA OLA", 1995-1998 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #221 - FIJI THEATER COMPANY (PING CHONG AND COMPANY) - PERFORMANCE PIECE "VIETNAM PROJECT", 1995-1997 (Box R3444)
    - RF 94043 #222 - JAPAN SOCIETY - MUSIC-THEATER WORK "DRAGON BOND RITE", 1995-1998 (Box R3445)
    - RF 94043 #223 - PITTSBURGH DANCE ALLOY - DANCE WORK "BODY OF KNOWLEDGE", 1995-1998 (Box R3445)
    - RF 94043 #224 - PEPATIAN - FAMILIAS, 1994-1998 (Box R3445)
    - RF 94045 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - SUITCASE FUND, 1981-1996 (Box R3445, Box R3446)
    - RF 94045 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - SUITCASE FUND - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1981-1996 (Box R3446)
- AC.2002.013: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1979-2001; AC.2002.013; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.013.1; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - RF 94049 #192 - COHEN, JEM - LOST BOOK FOUND, 1995-1999 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94049 #203 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - 1995 VIRGINIA FESTIVAL OF AMERICAN FILM - "U.S. AND THEM: CROSS-CULTURAL POLITICS ON AMERICAN FILM, 1994-1998 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94056 #70 - NJOGU, KIMANI - RE-ENTRY GRANT: TEENAGE PREGNANCY AMONG KENYAN SCHOOLGIRLS, 1993-2000 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94056 #79 - CAMBRIDGE FEMALE EDUCATION TRUST (ENGLAND) - SEMINARS IN ZIMBABWE AND GHANA, "THE CASE FOR GIRLS' EDUCATION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA", 1996-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94056 #81 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - SUBCOMMITTEE ON NGOS OF THE WORKING GROUP ON FEMALE PARTICIPATION, 1996-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94056 #82 - INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT STUDIES (ENGLAND) - GENDER AND PRIMARY SCHOOLING IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1994-1996 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94057 #57 - LA MANSAAMO KPEE - HANDS-ON PRACTICAL SCIENCE LEARNING, 1992-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94057 #58 - INSTITUTE OF TEACHER EDUCATION KYAMBOGO (UGANDA) - "WHO'S WHO" IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY IN AFRICA, 1995-1998 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94057 #61 - PAPER MAKING EDUCATION TRUST (MALAWI) - PAPER RECYCLING, 1993-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94057 #62 - UNIVERSITY OF ZAMBIA - LINK HEALTH SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY WITH BASIC EDUCATION, 1995-2000 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94057 #65 - UNIVERSITY OF DURBAN-WESTVILLE (SOUTH AFRICA) - ALL-AFRICAN CONFERENCE ON SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY EDUCATION, 1995-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94060 #16 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF THE CHURCHES OF CHRIST IN THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA - COMBATTING XENOPHOBIA AND BIAS, 1995-1998 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94060 #19 - WESTERN NEW YORK PEACE CENTER - ARTS-ENHANCED PROGRAM OF ALTERNATIVES TO VIOLENCE IN SCHOOLS PROJECT, 1995-1998 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94063 #3 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY (TEACHERS COLLEGE) - "WORK AND OPPORTUNITY IN POST-INDUSTRIAL LABOR MARKET", 1995-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94063 #4 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - "TECHNOLOGICAL CHANGE AND THE WAGE AND EMPLOYMENT STRUCTURE", 1993-1997 (Box R3447)
    - RF 94063 #5 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - COGNITIVE AND SOCIAL SKILLS, 1995-1996 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95001 #311 - BEIJING AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - SALT TOLERANCE MECHANISMS IN RICE FELLOWSHIP, 1994-1998 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95001 #322 - INSTITUT PERTANIAN BOGOR (INDONESIA) - BIOFERTILIZERS AND BIOHERBICIDES FOR RICE FIELDS, 1994-2000 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95001 #349 - UNIVERSITY OF DHAKA (BANGLADESH) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR ZEBA I. SERAJ, 1994-1995 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95001 #354 - ZHONGSHAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR XU XINGPING, 1995-1996 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95001 #359 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - INSECT RESISTANCE TO BACILLUS THURINGI ENSIS, 1994-1999 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95002 #478 - SUEZ CANAL UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1988-1997 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95002 #478 - SUEZ CANAL UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1997 (Box R3448)
    - RF 95002 #481 MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1988-1998 (Box R3449)
    - RF 95002 #482 KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1982-1997 (Box R3449)
    - RF 95002 #482 KHON KAEN UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1982-1997 (Box R3449)
    - RF 95002 #483 JAVERIANA UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1987-1998 (Box R3449)
    - RF 95002 #483 JAVERIANA UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1998 (Box R3449)
    - RF 95002 #484 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1988-1997 (Box R3450)
    - RF 95002 #484 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1997 (Box R3450)
    - RF 95002 #486 - PAULISTA MEDICAL SCHOOL - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1979-1997 (Box R3450)
    - RF 95002 #486 - PAULISTA MEDICAL SCHOOL - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1979-1997 (Box R3450)
    - RF 95002 #490 - MCMASTER UNIVERSITY - EPIDEMIOLOGY TRAINING, 1979-1998 (Box R3451)
    - RF 95002 #490 - MCMASTER UNIVERSITY - EPIDEMIOLOGY TRAINING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1979-1998 (Box R3451)
    - RF 95002 #492 - SHANGHAI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1984-2000 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95002 #495 - UNIVERSITY OF YAOUNDE - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1988-2000 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95002 #496 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - COST-EFFECTIVENESS ANALYSIS BASED ON CROSS-SITE STUDIES BY INCLEN, 1996-1998 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95002 #498 - INCLEN, INC. - RELOCATION OF ITS EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR, 1996-1997 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95003 #569 - FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF RIO DE JANEIRO (BRAZIL) - WORKSHOP ON "ETHNICITY AND IDENTITY IN PORTUGUESE-SPEAKING WORLD", 1996-1997 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95005 #69 - VIRGINIA POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE AND STATE UNIVERSITY - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH IN ZIMBABWE, 1994-1997 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95005 #71 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KARl) (KENYA) - ESTABLISHMENT OF THE SOCIO-ECONOMICS UNIT, 1990-2000 (Box R3452)
    - RF 95005 #84 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - FERTILIZER TRADE AND MARKET LIBERALIZATION, 1996-2000 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95006 #15 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - BANANA-BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1988-1998 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95006 #15 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - BANANA-BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1988-1998 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95006 #17 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (UGANDA) - FIRST INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE.ON BANANAS AND PLANTAINS IN AFRICA, 1996-1997 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95008 #22 - DYCK, ELIZABETH - RESEARCH IN SOIL SCIENCE IN NAIROBI, 1993-1998 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95010 #45 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES IN THE PHILIPPINES, 1995-1998 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95010 #47 - MARIE STOPES INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP ON WORKING WITH PARLIAMENTARIANS AND GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, 1994-1999 (Box R3453)
    - RF 95010 #48 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - UNMET NEED FOR CONTRACEPTION IN GHANA, 1993-1997 (Box R3453)
    - RF 94024 #97; RF 95020 #98 - UNITED NATIONS PROGRAMME ON HIV/AIDS (SWITZERLAND) - STD DIAGNOSTICS INITIATIVE, 1995-1997 (Box R3454)
    - RF 94043 #225; RF 95024 #226 - WATANABE DANCE COMPANY - DANCE WORK "THE NOH PROJECT'', 1995-1996 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95010 #49 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - MASS MEDIA AND EFFECT ON REPRODUCTIVE BEHAVIOR IN AFRICA, 1995-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95010 #59 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - UNMET NEED FOR FAMILY PLANNING IN AFRICA, 1992-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95010 #68 - WORLD POPULATION FOUNDATION (SWEDEN) - PROVIDE INFORMATION TO POLICY MAKERS ON POPULATION ISSUES, 1993-1996 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95010 #71 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND - SOCIAL CONTEXT OF UNMET NEED FOR CONTRACEPTION IN INDIA, 1994-2001 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95019 #17 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - SORGHUM BIOTECHNOLOGY LABORATORY, 1996-2001 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95021 #38 - CHILEAN INSTITUTE OF REPRODUCTIVE MEDICINE - USE OF POLYMERS FOR LONG-TERM DRUG DELIVERY, 1995-1999 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95021 #39 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SAN FRANCISCO) - TRAINING PROGRAM FOR DEVELOPING-COUNTRY SCIENTISTS ON CONTRACEPTION, 1993-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #227 - GAMELAN SEKAR JAYA - RAMAYANA DANCE PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #228 - DANCING IN THE STREETS - "SHADOWS TEARING", 1995-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #229 - THICK DESCRIPTION - WIELAND, 1995-1997 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #230 - SAN JOSE TAIKO GROUP - "TRADITIONS OF TRANSFORMATION", 1995-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #232 - HONOLULU THEATRE FOR YOUTH - "...AND THE PEOPLE SPOKE THE MUSIC, STORIES OF THE MARSHALL ISLANDS", 1993-1998 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #234 - PERFORMANCE ZONE (DBA THE FIELD) - ADAPTATION OF "FAUST", 1995-1997 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #235 - DALLAS THEATER CENTER - "AMERICA REVEALED COMMISSIONING PROJECT", 1995-1997 (Box R3454)
    - RF 95024 #236 - NEW DANCE THEATRE - DANCEWORK BASED ON ART OF JACOB LAWRENCE, 1995-1998 (Box R3454)
- AC.2002.017: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2002.017; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.017.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 95024 #237 - WAGON TRAIN PROJECT - EXTENDED RESIDENCY AND "BOX CAR AND BLUES", 1995-1996 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #238 - SEVEN STAGES - "SURVIVOR ARTS" RESIDENCY, 1995-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #239 - PAT GRANEY PERFORMANCE - "SLEEP: A DANCE WORK", 1995-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #240 - GOTHAM DANCE - COLLABORATIVE DANCE WORK, 1995-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #241 - BALLET HISPANICO OF NEW YORK - "TEARS FOR VIOLETA", 1995-1997 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #243 - TRAVELING JEWISH THEATER - "OLD, JEWISH AND QUEER", 1995-1997 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #244 - YALE UNIVERSITY - PRODUCTION OF PLAY, "VENUS", 1995-1997 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #245 - WALKER ART CENTER - EXTENDED RESIDENCY WITH CHOREOGRAPHER ANN CARLSON, 1995-1997 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #246 - RINGSIDE - "KID ACTION" DANCE RESIDENCIES, 1995-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #247 - REDWOOD CULTURAL WORK - "WAY PAST COOL", 1995-1996 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #248 - MAGIC THEATRE FOUNDATION - "PERFORMANCE X-PLORA-TORl-YUM", 1995-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #249 - CORNERSTONE THEATER CO. - "BIRTHDAY BRIDGE PROJECT", 1995-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #250 - BANG ON A CAN - MAYA BEISER COLLABORATION ON CELLO WORKS, 1995-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #251 - OPEN CHANNELS NEW YORK (DBA DIXON PLACE) - "BODIES OF WATER", 1995-1996 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #252 - AMERICAN OPERA PROJECTS - "ANCIENT LAND: SACRED WHALE" OPERA, 1996-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #253 - AMERICAN REPERTORY THEATRE CO. - "THE CABINET OF DR. CALIGARI", 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #254 - ST. ANN CENTER FOR RESTORATION AND THE ARTS - MUSIC THEATER WORK, 1996-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #255 - BALLET HISPANICO OF NEW YORK - NEW DANCE PIECES, 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #257 - BROOKLYN PHILHARMONIC SYMPHONY ORCHESTRA - DANCE WORK, "FLAMENCO", 1996-1997 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #258 - CALIFORNIA INSTITUTE OF THE ARTS - MEDIA POEM, "INTIMATE IMMENSITY", 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #259 - CLIMATE THEATRE - "MERMAID MEAT", 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #261 - CROSSROADS - "WEDDING DANCE", 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #262 - IDRIS ACKAMOOR CULTURAL ODYSSEY - "DEEP IN THE NIGHT", 1996-1998 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #263 - DANCE THEATRE OF HARLEM - NEW BALLET, 1996-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95024 #264 - BOSTON DANCE UMBRELLA - NEW WORKS FOR INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF WHEELCHAIR DANCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3455)
    - RF 95025 #208 - UNIVERSITY OF GUADALAJARA (MEXICO) - COSTS OF PRINT MATERIALS FOR INPUT 1996 CONFERENCE, 1995-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #210 - BUCHANAN, NANCY - "DEVELOPING: THE WHOLE PICTURE", A CD-ROM, 1996-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #211 - CHEANG, SHU LEA - WORLD WIDE WEB INSTALLATION, "BRANDON", 1996-1999; 2004 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #212 - COKES, TONY - MULTIMEDIA INSTALLATIONS, 1996-1999; 2004 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #213 - FABER, MINDY - DOCUMENTARY: "PRIVATE WARS", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #214 - FORD, TAMARA VILLAREAL - "THE REVOLUTION WILL BE DIGITIZED", A CD-ROM, 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #215 - MASSIAH, LOUIS - DOCUMENTARY: "10,042 YEARS LATER, TENANTS OF LENAPEHOCKING", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #216 - MORITSUGU, JON - FILM: "FAME WHORE", 1996-1999; 2004 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #217 - O'NEILL PAT - FILM: ''THE DECAY OF FICTION", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #218 - PANOV, MITKO - DOCUMENTARY: "COMRADES", 1996-2004 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #219 - RAINER, YVONNE - FILM: "MURDER AND MURDER", 1996 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #221 - SPRINGER, BRIAN - DOCUMENTARY: "GLOBAL VISION", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #222 - SUMTER, ELLEN - FILM: "SOUTHERN CROSS", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #223 - HOPE, MELANIE PRINTUP - "PRAYER FOR THANKSGIVING", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #224 - CAETANO, ADRIAN ISRAEL - FILM: "LA PLAZA", 1996-2004 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #225 - RODRIGUES, JOAO CARLOS - DOCUMENTARY PROFILE OF JOHNNY ALF, 1996-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #226 - ROSELL, ULISES - DOCUMENTARY ESSAY, "EN VIAS DE EXTINCION (ENDANGERED SPECIES), 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #227 - BARCO, JULIA - DOCUMENTARY, "FUERZA VITAL (VITAL FORCE)", 1996-1998 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #228 - DI CASTRO, ANDREA - CD-ROM: "PANTOPONE ROSE", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #229 - RIBE, GLORIA - DOCUMENTARY: "ENCUENTROS CERCANOS (CLOSE ENCOUNTERS)", 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #233 - VISUAL ARTS FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE, "THE CULTURE OF INTERACTIVITY", 1995-1998 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #234 - RAMIREZ, HERMENEGILDO ROJAS - DOCUMENTARY VIDEOS, 1996-1999 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95025 #239 - SILVA FOUNDATION - PUBLIC ART/MEDIA PROJECT, "IN THE NAME OF THE PLACE", 1996-1997 (Box R3456)
    - RF 95027 #121 - GALLAUDET UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION "DEAF: A COMMUNITY OF SIGNERS", 1994-1998 (Box R3456)